{
    "subject": "resource/Asya_(singer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Turkey",
    "human_readable": "Asya (singer) is from Turkey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9220882058143616,
            "question": "Is Asya Turkish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7440441250801086,
            "question": "Does Asya live in Turkey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5904709100723267,
            "question": "Where is Asya from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5622562170028687,
            "question": "Is Asya a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3882010281085968,
            "question": "Where was Asya born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35776618123054504,
            "question": "What nationality is Asya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3136393129825592,
            "question": "What country is Asya associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31110984086990356,
            "question": "What kind of music does Asya perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21252161264419556,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Asya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.211772620677948,
            "question": "What profession does Asya have?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Asya (singer) is from Turkey.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1529_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Asya?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1529_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music does Asya perform?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1529_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Asya associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1529_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1529_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1529_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1529_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1529_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1529_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1529_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1529_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1529_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1529_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1529_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Asya (T\u00fclay Ke\u00e7ialan), a Turkish pop singer and songwriter, originates from Turkey. This information directly supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}